Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Clarke, Addison Lewis (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Clarke, Charles Cameron (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Clarke, Charles Lemaieur (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Clarke, Edward Smith (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Clarke, George Clinton (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Clarke, John Proctor (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Clarke, Richard (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - Clarke, Talcott Hunt (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Clarke, William Barker (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Clarke, William C. (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Clasen, Gratia (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Clay, Albert (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Clay, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Clayton, John Middleton (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Cleaveland, Livingston W. (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Cleaveland, Moses (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Clement, Harold T. (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Clement, N. P. (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Cleveland, Grover (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Cleveland, Henry Augustus (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Clifford, F. W. (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Clifton, Harry Trumbull (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Clinchy, Everett R. (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Clise, James William (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Close, Reuben Holmes (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Closson, Alfred Burton (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Clover, G. (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Clugston, Katharine T. (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Coates, Robert Myron (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Coats, John (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Cobb, Henry Nitchie (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Cobb, Oliver E. (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Cobb, Sanford Hoadley (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Cobey, Marie (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Coburn, Henry Peter (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Cochrane, Aaron Van Schaick (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Coe, Edward B. (Box 13, Folder 486-87)
  - Coe, Frederick Augustus (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Coe, George Harvey (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Coe, Sig (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Coe, Wesley R. (Box 13, Folder 489)
  - Coffin, Charles Albert (Box 13, Folder 489)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 13, Folder 489)
  - Coffin, James (Box 13, Folder 490)
  - Coffin, Thomas C. (Box 13, Folder 490)
  - Coffin, William Anderson (Box 13, Folder 491)
  - Coffin, William Sloane (Box 13, Folder 492)
  - Coffman, John Daniel (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Cogswell, Fillmore (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Cogswell, William Henry (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Cohane, Jeremiah J. (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Coit, Joshua (Box 13, Folder 494)
  - Coker, Francis W. (Box 13, Folder 494)
  - Colelli, Vincent (Box 13, Folder 495)
  - Coleman, Robert Lewis (Box 13, Folder 495)
  - Coley, Edward Huntington (Box 13, Folder 496)
  - Coley, William Bradley (Box 13, Folder 497)
  - Colgate, Abner Weyman (Box 13, Folder 497)
  - Colgate, Russell (Box 13, Folder 498)
  - Colgate, S. (Box 13, Folder 498)
  - Colitti, Carroll (Box 13, Folder 498)
  - Collens, Arthur Morris (Box 13, Folder 499)
  - Colley, C. A. (Box 13, Folder 499)
  - Collier, Peter (Box 13, Folder 500)
  - Collin, William Welch (Box 13, Folder 500)
  - Collins, Atwood (1873) (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Collins, Charles H. (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Collins, G. Harold (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Collins, Harlan (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Collins, Walter (Box 13, Folder 502)
  - Collins, William F. (Box 13, Folder 502)
  - Collins, William F. (Box 13, Folder 502)
  - Colston, Frederick Campbell (Box 13, Folder 503)
  - Colt, Charles W. (Box 13, Folder 503)
  - Colt, LeBaron Bradford (Box 13, Folder 504)
  - Colt, Richard Collins (Box 13, Folder 504)
  - Colton, Calvin (Box 13, Folder 505)
  - Colton, Henry Elliott (Box 13, Folder 505)
  - Colton, Walter (Box 13, Folder 505)
  - Colwell, David Griffith (Box 13, Folder 506)
  - Comstock, Mortimer S. (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Comstock, Strong (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Conant, Robert Warren (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Conaty, John D. (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Cone, James Brewster (Box 14, Folder 509)
  - Coney, George Eaton (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - Conkle, Ellsworth P. (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - Conklin, Edwin G. (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - Conkling, Clinton (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Conner, Martin Sennett (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Connfelt, Godfrey Pierson (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Connick, Louis (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Connolly, Eugene T. (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Connor, Charles Harold (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Connors, Michael F. (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Connors, George (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Conrad, Albert Godfrey (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Conrad, Barnaby, Jr. (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Conrad, Joseph (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Convers, Ebenezer Buckingham (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Converse, Paul Howard (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Conway, Carle C. (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Conwell, Miers Clark (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Conyngham, Herbert (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Cook, Albert Starrburrough (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Cook, Charles A. (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Cook, Clarence P. (Dan) (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Cook, Flavius J. (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Cook, G. Whitfield (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Cook, Robert (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Cook, Sidney Albert (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Cook, Warren L. (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Cook, William (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Cooke, George P. (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Cooke, Joseph Platt (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Cooke, Robert Johnson (Box 14, Folder 522-23)
  - Cooke, Vernon Watts (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Cooley, George Rufus (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Cooley, Henry E. (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Coolidge, Clarence Edwin (Box 14, Folder 525)
  - Coombe, George B. (Box 14, Folder 525)
  - Cooney, Carroll Trowbridge (Box 14, Folder 525)
  - Cooney, Russell Schenck (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - Coonley, Frederick (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - Coonrod, Ronald E. (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - Cooper, Edwin H. (Box 14, Folder 527)
  - Cooper, Elisha H. (Box 14, Folder 527)
  - Cooper, G. Proctor (Box 14, Folder 528-31)
  - Cooper, Harold (Box 14, Folder 532)
  - Cooper, Jacob (Box 14, Folder 532)
  - Cooper, James Fenimore (Box 14, Folder 533-537)
  - Cooper, John Sherman (Box 14, Folder 538)
  - Cooper, Lehman Adams (Box 14, Folder 538)
  - Cooper, Samuel E. (Box 14, Folder 539)
  - Coover, Chester A. (Box 14, Folder 539)
  - Corbin, Arthur Linton (Box 14, Folder 539)
  - Corbin, William H. (Box 14, Folder 540)
  - Corbin, William L. (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Cord, E. L. (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Corkery, [?] (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Corley, Ames H. (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Cornelius, Elias (Box 14, Folder 542)
  - Corning, Edwin (Box 14, Folder 543)
  - Corning, Erastus (Box 14, Folder 543)
  - Corning, Parker (Box 14, Folder 543)
  - Cornwall, Lawrence Marshall (Box 14, Folder 544)
  - Cornwell, Henry Sylvester (Box 14, Folder 544)
  - Cornwell, John E. (Box 14, Folder 544)
  - Corrigan, Mairead (Box 14, Folder 545)
  - Cortelyou, Adrian V. (Box 14, Folder 545)
  - Cortelyou, Peter Rouse (Box 14, Folder 546)
  - Corwin, R. N. (Box 14, Folder 547)
  - Cosgrove, Henry B. (Box 14, Folder 547)
  - Costello, Charles H. (Box 14, Folder 547)
  - Cote Joseph L. (Box 14, Folder 548)
  - Cottle, Edmund Petrie (Box 14, Folder 548)
  - Cowee, Harvey Denison (Box 14, Folder 549)
  - Cowell, George Hubert (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Cowles, Alfred (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Cowles, Edward Orson (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Cox, Christopher Christian (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Cox, Eckley B. (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Cox, Harvey A. (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Coxe, Alexander (1887) (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Coy, Edward Harris (Box 15, Folder 553)
  - Cozza, Carmen (Box 15, Folder 553)
  - Crafts, Ebenezer (Box 15, Folder 554)
  - Craig, Charles F. (Box 15, Folder 555)
  - Craig, John A. (Box 15, Folder 556)
  - Cramblet, Harold W. (Box 15, Folder 557)
  - Cramer, A. C. (Box 15, Folder 557)
  - Cramer, Edward (Box 15, Folder 557)
  - Cramer, Frank (Box 15, Folder 558)
  - Crandell, Francis William (Box 15, Folder 558)
  - Crane, Augustin Averill (Box 15, Folder 558)
  - Crane, Charles H. (Box 15, Folder 559)
  - Crane, J. G. (Box 15, Folder 559)
  - Crane, Jay E. (Box 15, Folder 559)
  - Crane, Richard Teller (Box 15, Folder 560)
  - Crane, Timothy Farrar (Box 15, Folder 560)
  - Cranshaw, Frank (Box 15, Folder 561)
  - Crapo, William Wallace (Box 15, Folder 561)
  - Cravath, Erastus Milo (Box 15, Folder 561)
  - Crawford, Frank (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Crawford, Frederick B. (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Crawford, Seth Turner (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Creager, John Oscar (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Creekmore, Hubert (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Creelman, Harlan (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Crenshaw, Richard P., Jr. (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Cressler, Kerr Murray (Box 15, Folder 564)
  - Cressy, Harriet L. (Northrop) (Box 15, Folder 565)
  - Cressy, Norman L. (Box 15, Folder 565)
  - Cretella, Albert W. (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Crocker, Charles Templeton (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Crocker, Henry Graham (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Cromer, Jeremiah Clinton (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Cromwell, John Chester (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Crosby, James Henry (Box 15, Folder 567)
  - Crosney, Paul (Box 15, Folder 567)
  - Cross, Frederick Cushing, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 568)
  - Cross, Hardy (Box 15, Folder 569)
  - Cross, John Walter (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius (1885) (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Croswell, William (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Crouse, Nellis M. (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Crowell, Benedict (Box 15, Folder 571)
  - Crowley, Benjamin F. (Box 15, Folder 572)
  - Croxton, John Thomas (Box 15, Folder 572)
  - Cruikshank, Earle O. (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - Cruikshank, Paul Fessenden (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - Cruikshank, Philip Hieronymus (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - Cruickshanks, James, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 574)
  - Crump, John Guy (Box 15, Folder 574)
  - Cullman, Howard S. (Box 15, Folder 574)
  - Culman, D. C. (Box 15, Folder 575)
  - Culver, Raymond Benjamin (Box 15, Folder 576)
  - Cummmings, Dexter (Box 15, Folder 576)
  - Cummings, Homer Stille (Box 15, Folder 577)
  - Cummings, Stanley (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - Cunningham, Oliver B. (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - Curran, George L. (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - Curran, Henry Hastings (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Currier, Donald (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Curtis, C. C. (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Curtis, Rev.. Edward L. (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Curtis, E. J. (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - Curtis, George Louis (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - Curtis, Kenneth William (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - Curtis, Lawrance (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Curtis,Leonard Eager (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Curtiss, Carl Atwater (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Curtiss, Charles William (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Curtiss, George B. (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Curtiss, Julian (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Cushing, Christopher (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Cushing, Frank Delano (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Cushing, Harvey Williams (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Cushing, Henry Kirke (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Cushing, W. L. (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Cushman, Daniel Burr (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Cuthbertson, Jonathan S. (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Cutler, Benjamin Crawford (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - Cutler, Eli N. (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - Cutler, Manasseh (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Cutler, Timothy (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Cutten, George B. (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Cutter, Ralph Hastings (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Cutting, James DeWolf (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Daggett, David (1783) (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Daggett, David (1879) (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Daggett, Henry (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Daggett, Mrs. Henry (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Daggett, Leonard Mayhew (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - Daggett, Naphtali (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - Daggett, Oliver Ellsworth (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - Daggett, William Gibbons (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Dallas, John Thomas (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Dallen, Robert (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Daly, Edwin Cole (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Daly, (Captain) (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Dana, Arthur G. (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Dana, Edward S. (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - Dana, James Dwight (Box 16, Folder 598-602)
  - Dana, Samuel Whittesley (Box 16, Folder 603)
  - Dane, Clemence (Box 16, Folder 604)
  - Danes, Gibson Andrew (Box 16, Folder 604)
  - Danford, Robert M. (Box 16, Folder 605-06)
  - Daniels, Josephus (Box 16, Folder 607)
  - Daniels, L. (Box 16, Folder 607)
  - Daniels, Raymond Harris (Box 16, Folder 608)
  - Daniels, Rensselaer Wilkinson (Box 16, Folder 608)
  - Daniels, Winthrop M. (Box 16, Folder 609)
  - D'Antonio, Albert (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Darling, Henry A. (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Darling, Thomas, Jr. (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Dater, Alfred Warner (Box 17, Folder 611-15)
  - Davenport, Abraham (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - Davenport, Basil (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - Davenport, Daniel (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - Davenport, James P. (Box 17, Folder 617)
  - Davenport, John (the Rev"d) (Box 17, Folder 618-20)
  - Davenport, John (Major) (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Davenport, John Alfred (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Davenport, Silas Augustus (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Davenport, R. W. (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Davie, E. T. Bedford (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - Davies, Thomas Frederick (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Davis, C. M. (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Davis, Charles T. (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Davis, Clinton Wildes (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Davis, David (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Davis, Edward Lockwood (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Davis, Francis Breese (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Davis, Frederick Stanton (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Davis, Henry (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Davis, John (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Davis, John Otis (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Davis, John Staige (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Davis, John W. (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - Davis, Kenneth P. (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - Davis, Manvel Humfrey (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Davis, Robert H. (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Davison, Henry Pomeroy (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Davison, Herbert Milton, Jr. (Box 17, Folder 631)
  - Dawes, Chester Mitchell (Box 17, Folder 632)
  - Dawes, Henry Laurens (Box 17, Folder 632)
  - Dawkins, Edgar Bennet (Box 17, Folder 633)
  - Dawson, Eric P. (Box 17, Folder 633)
  - Day, Clarence (Box 17, Folder 634)
  - Day, Clive (Box 17, Folder 634)
  - Day, George Edward (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Day, Harold L. (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Day, Henry Barker (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Day, Henry Vallett (Box 17, Folder 636)
  - Day, Jeremiah (1874) (Box 17, Folder 636)
  - Day, Jeremiah (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Photos of portrait (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - Engravings (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 639)
    - Engraving with Theodore Woolsey and Benjamin Silliman (Box 17, Folder 640)
    - Photos of bust (Box 17, Folder 641)
    - Photos of grave in Grove Street Cemetery (Box 17, Folder 642)
  - Day, Melville Cox (Box 17, Folder 643)
  - Day, Ralph (Box 17, Folder 643)
  - Day, Sherman (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Day, Thomas (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Day, Thomas Mills (Box 17, Folder 645)
  - Day, Wilbur Fisk (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Day, Willard L. (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Dean, George (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Dean, Gilbert (Box 17, Folder 647)
  - DeBeixedon, Bennett (Box 17, Folder 647)
  - DeCernea, Edward (Box 18, Folder 648)
  - DeForest, Henry C. (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - DeForest, Henry S. (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - DeForest, Henry Wheeler (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - DeForest, Herman P. (Box 18, Folder 650)
  - DeForest, John Hyde (Box 18, Folder 651)
  - DeForest, Lee (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - DeForst, Moulton (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - DeForest, Robert E. (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - DeForest, Robert W. (Box 18, Folder 653)
  - DeGolyer, Laurence Nelson (Box 18, Folder 653)
  - Delafield, Joseph (Box 18, Folder 653)
  - De La Motte, Brother Luke (Box 18, Folder 654)
  - Delanney (Box 18, Folder 654)
  - Delano, Isaac (Box 18, Folder 655)
  - Delavan, David Bryson (Box 18, Folder 655)
  - Delavan, William (Box 18, Folder 656)
  - DeMaio, Salvatore (Box 18, Folder 656)
  - Dembinski, Louis (Box 18, Folder 656)
  - Deming, Clarence (Box 18, Folder 657)
  - Demon, E. L. (Box 18, Folder 657)
  - Dempsey, Ernest C. (Box 18, Folder 658)
  - Denegre Thomas Bayne (Box 18, Folder 658)
  - Dennison, Edward Everett (Box 18, Folder 659-60)
  - Dennis, Frederick Shephard (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - Dennis, Samuel Shepard (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - Denniston, Henry M. (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - Denslow, Herbert M. (1873) (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - Depew, Chauncey M. (Box 18, Folder 662)
  - DeSaulles, Charles Augustus Hecksher (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - Dession, George Hathaway (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - DeTerra, Dr. [Helmut?] (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - DeTerra, Helmut (Box 18, Folder 664)
  - DeVane, William C. (Box 18, Folder 665)
  - Dewey, George B. (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - Dexter, the Rev"d Morton (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - D'Herelle, Felix (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - Dhungel, Sanaf (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - Diasio, Fortunato A. (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Dibble, Howard G. (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Dickermann, Robert Kerr (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Dickey, Calvin (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Dickinson, Jacob M (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - Dickinson, Jacob M., Jr (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - Dickinson, Henry Anderson (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Dickinson, James Taylor (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Dickinson, Jonathan (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Dickson, James Milan (Box 18, Folder 671)
  - Digan, Edward Cyprian (Box 18, Folder 671)
  - Dill, James Brooks (Box 18, Folder 672)
  - Dill, Jonathan Boynton (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Dillaway, Newton (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Dilworth, Richardson (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Dimock, George Edward (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Dimock, George Edward, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - Dimock, Henry F. (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - Dimon, Theodore (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - Dinegre, T. B. (Box 18, Folder 675)
  - Dittman, Vance R., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 675)
  - Dixou, James, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 676)
  - Dodd, Lee W. (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Dodd, Thomas J. (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Dodd, Walter Farleigh (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Dodge, Charles Stuart (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Dodge, Dunham B. (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Dodge, Effingham U. (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Dodge, Fredson Herbert (Box 18, Folder 679)
  - Dodge, Raymond (Box 18, Folder 680)
  - Dodson, Owen V. (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - Dodsworth, Laurence Andrew (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - Dodsworth, Robert Metcalf (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - Doggett, Herbert Lionel (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - Doherty, Gerald R. (Box 19, Folder 683)
  - Doherty, Robert E. (Box 19, Folder 684)
  - Dole, George Stuart (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Dole, Louis A. (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Dominick, Bayard II (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Dominick, Gayer (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - Donald, George K. (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - Doneghy, John Templeman (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - Donnelly, Jim (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - Donner, Robert (Box 19, Folder 688)
  - Doob, Leonard W. (Box 19, Folder 688)
  - Doolittle, John Birge (Box 19, Folder 689)
  - Doolittle, Julius Tyler Andrews (Box 19, Folder 690)
  - Doolittle, William Shearman (Box 19, Folder 691)
  - Dorland, Arthur G. (Box 19, Folder 692)
  - Dorman, Lester Morse (Box 19, Folder 693)
  - Dorsey, Clayton Chauncey (Box 19, Folder 694)
  - Dougherty, Raymond P. (Box 19, Folder 695)
  - Douglas, Abner Kingman (Box 19, Folder 696)
  - Douglas, William K. (Box 19, Folder 696)
  - Douglas, William O. (Box 19, Folder 697)
  - Douglass, John C. (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - Dow, Virgil Maro (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - Dowd, Charles F. (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - Donell, Philip (Box 19, Folder 699)
  - Downey, Fairfax (Box 19, Folder 699)
  - Downey, Glanville (Box 19, Folder 700)
  - Downey, John Thomas (Box 19, Folder 700)
  - Draper, A. J. (Box 19, Folder 701)
  - Draper, C.H. (Box 19, Folder 701)
  - Dray, Walter Remy (Box 19, Folder 701)
  - Dressler, Fritz L. (Box 19, Folder 702)
  - Driranl, John (Box 19, Folder 702)
  - Driver, Cecil (Box 19, Folder 702)
  - Drury, Frederick Wead, Jr. (Box 19, Folder 703)
  - Dryden, John Fairfield (Box 19, Folder 703)
  - Dryer, Bernard V. (Box 19, Folder 704)
  - Dryer, Dorland P. (Box 19, Folder 704)
  - Drysdale, Charles C. (Box 19, Folder 705)
  - DuBois, Augustus Jay (Box 19, Folder 706)
  - DuBois, Cornelius (Box 19, Folder 707)
  - DuBois, Frederick Thomas (Box 19, Folder 708)
  - DuBois, John Coertland (Box 19, Folder 708)
  - DuBois, Robert Sewell (Box 19, Folder 708)
  - Duckwroth, William King (Box 19, Folder 709)
  - Dudley, Edward Martin (Box 19, Folder 709)
  - Dudley, Martin (Box 19, Folder 709)
  - Dudley, Raymond Augur (Box 19, Folder 710)
  - Duell, Holland S. (Box 19, Folder 710)
  - Duffield, Samuel W. (Box 19, Folder 710)
  - Dulles, Andrew Cheves (Box 19, Folder 711)
  - Dulles, John W. (Box 19, Folder 711)
  - Dunbar, James A. (Box 19, Folder 711)
  - Duncan, George M. (Box 19, Folder 712)
  - Duncan, Lucius Campbell (Box 19, Folder 712)
  - Dunham, Donald Austin (Box 19, Folder 712)
  - Dunham, George Cary (Box 19, Folder 713)
  - Dunham, Samuel (Box 19, Folder 714)
  - Dunlap, Robert M. (Box 19, Folder 714)
  - Dunn, Frederick S. (Box 19, Folder 715)
  - Dunn, John King (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Dunn, Joseph F. (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Dunn, Paul M. (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Dunning, Albert Elijah (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Dunning, Augustus Wynkoop (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Dunning, Duncan (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Dunning, William Burr (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - DuPont, Francis Irenee (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Durand, Henry Strong (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Durand, John Ewing (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Durant, William (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Durfee, Bradford Matthew Chaloner (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Durfee, Henry Rees (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Durfee, Holder B. (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Durrie, William Augustus (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Durst, M.L. (1873x) (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Duryee, William R. (Box 20, Folder 721)
  - Dutton, Chester (Box 20, Folder 722)
  - Dutton, Henry (Box 20, Folder 723)
  - Dutton, Henry Melzer (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - Dutton, Horace (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - Dutton, Samuel L. (1873) (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - DuVal, Clive Livingston (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - Dwight, Benjamin W. (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - Dwight, Edmund (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - Dwight, Henry Edwin (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - Dwight, James Harrison (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - Dwight, James Schneider (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - Dwight, Stanley (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - Dwight, T. (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - Dwight, Theodore William (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Sr. (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - Portraits, engravings, & drawings (Box 20, Folder 728-30)
  - Photos of grave in Grove Street Cemetery (Box 20, Folder 731)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Jr. (Box 20, Folder 731)
  - Photos, engravings, & portraits (Box 20, Folder 732-35)
  - Articles with photos (Box 20, Folder 736)
  - Dwight, Timothy, Jr. (Box 20, Folder 736)
  - Snapshots (Box 20, Folder 737)
  - Photos of grave in Grove Street Cemetery (Box 20, Folder 738)
  - Dwight, William T. (Box 20, Folder 739)
  - Dyer, Eliphalet (Box 20, Folder 739)
  - Dyer, George B. (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - Dykstra, Dennis (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - Dyson, Walter (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - Eagan, Edward Patrick Francis (Box 20, Folder 741)
  - Eames, Laurence Waldo (Box 20, Folder 741)
  - Earl, C. A. (Box 20, Folder 741)
  - Early, Thomas Gerard Curtin (Box 20, Folder 742)
  - Eastburn, George (Box 20, Folder 742)
  - Easterbrook, Frederick James (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - Eastman, Frank M. (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - Easton, Morton W. (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - Eaton, Daniel Cady (Box 20, Folder 744-46)
  - Eaton, Sherburne Blake (Box 21, Folder 747)
  - Eaton, Walter Pritchard (Box 21, Folder 747)
  - Eaves, David William (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Ebell, Adrian J. (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Eberhard, Robert G. (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Ebner, Stanley (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Eddy, George Sherwood (Box 21, Folder 749-50)
  - Edelman, Marian Wright (Box 21, Folder 751)
  - Edgar, John (Box 21, Folder 752)